跟上舞步啊  霍华德
Try to keep up, Howard!
哥舞力全开呢
I'm killing it!
真希望我们在舞厅跳舞时
Yeah, I wish we looked as cool dancing in clubs
跟现在一样帅
as we do right now.
别担心  你们在舞厅跳舞时
Don't worry, this is exactly how you look
就是你们现在这副样
when you're dancing in clubs.
女士们  不用谢
You're welcome, ladies.
超大新闻啊  男士们
Paradigm-shifting news, gentlemen!
兄弟
Dude!
我正要上前舞翻那骚妞呢
I was about to Bollywood this bitch.
早先
Earlier today,
我邀请了史蒂芬·霍金教授与我玩
I invited Professor Stephen Hawking to join me
风靡网络的小游戏《填字游戏》
in the popular online game Words with Friends.
跨平台的知名线上填字游戏
游戏名字还有  与朋友谈话/吵架[填字]的意思
他刚刚同意了我的游戏邀请
Moments ago, he accepted my request.
你们知道这代表什么意思吗
Do you understand what that means?
霍金教授正在地球上的某处说着
That somewhere right now Stephen Hawking is saying,
"靠
"Damn it.
我本来是要按拒绝的"
I meant to click no."
我来解释给你们听吧
I'll walk you through it.
这游戏可不是叫"与陌生人玩填字"
The game is not called Words with Strangers.
也不是叫
No, it's not even called
"与相识的人玩填字"
Words with Acquaintances.
而是叫"与...
It is called Words with...
我才不接你的话
I'm not finishing your sentence.
哥舞翻全场时  你居然关我游戏
You pulled the plug on my funk.
"与朋友"
Friends!
是"与朋友玩填字"游戏
It's Words with Friends!
代表着我与霍金正式成为朋友了
Which Stephen Hawking and I officially are.
只要再拥有个双层床与溜滑梯
Now all I need is a bunk bed with a slide;
我六岁时就许下的愿望
I'll have everything I've ever wanted
就全都圆满了
since I was six years old.
谢尔顿  那挺好啊
That's really nice, Sheldon.
我也替你开心
I'm happy for you.
And I'm happy for you, too.
因为你现在成了
You are now friends with someone
史蒂芬·霍金朋友的朋友
who is officially friends with Stephen Hawking.
慢慢乐吧  同志们
Enjoy it, boys.
可能是你们人生的最高点啊
You may have peaked.
谢尔顿  我也认识史蒂芬·霍金
Sheldon, I know Stephen Hawking.
我与他共事过
I worked with him.
等哪天出了款
And if they ever come out with a game called
"与曾共事过的人玩填字"的游戏
Words with People You Once Worked with,
才轮你上场
you'll be off to the races.
谢尔顿  玩个游戏也不代表...
Sheldon, I don't think this actually means...
话别说太早
Hold that thought!
"霍金教授下了一步"
Professor Hawking has made a move.
哎哟妈呀
Boy, oh boy.
要不了多久
Oh, it's only a matter of time
我们俩就会开始互取好玩绰号了
before we're coming up with fun nicknames for each other.
他喊我"鸡笼弟"
I'll be Coop.
我叫他"轮子哥"
He'll be Wheels.
前提是他不介意的话啦
If he's okay with that.
好的
All right.
开大空调吧
Crank up the AC, boy!
哥要热翻全场啦
It's gonna get hot in here!
今早我洗了个澡
So, I was taking a shower this morning,
洗完出来  就拿起了旁边
and when I got out, I started to dry off with
看似浴巾的东西擦身子
what I thought was a towel
结果发现那是霍华德他妈的内裤
but turned out to be Howard's mom's underwear.
害我得重洗了一次澡
I had to take another shower.
但洗了也没用
It wasn't enough.
洗得了身子  洗不去创伤
Nothing will ever be enough.
有一次我瞧了谢尔顿的内裤抽屉
I once looked in Sheldon's underwear drawer.
被他骂了
He yelled at me.
但那份内裤的记忆将永存我心
But now I know what it looks like
他收不回也抢不走
and he can never take that away.
这下面有本书呢
There's a book under here.
我自己捡吧
Oh, I'll get that.
-不用  我捡到了  -别  那是...
- I got it. I got it. - No, no, it's...
你怎么会有一本历史课本啊
Why do you have a history textbook?
没什么啦
It's not a big deal.
我就去了帕萨迪纳社区大学上课嘛
Just taking a class at the Pasadena Community College.
这很好啊
That's great.
我都不知道你还想再读书
I didn't know you wanted to go back to school.
只是上个历史课啦
It's just one history class.
当年没读完大学
Look, I didn't finish college,
就想说再试一下
so I thought I would give it a try.
反正你的演艺事业
Not to mention, your acting career
也如同佘曼将军  一路向南[失败]
is going south like Sherman.
威廉·特库姆塞·佘曼
美国南北战争中的北部联邦军将领
翻你的历史课本就懂了
Read about it in your book.
为什么不好意思告诉我们呢
Why would you be embarrassed to tell us?
不是的  我是不想让任何人知道
No, I'm not embarrassed. I just didn't want anyone to know
我还没告诉莱纳德嘛
because I haven't told Leonard yet.
那你为什么不告诉他呢
Why wouldn't you tell Leonard?
他听到他女朋友重回学校
Because it's me going back to school,
肯定会说"你行的"  "我怎么帮你呢"
and he's gonna be all "You can do it," and "How can I help?"
以及"我超以你为荣"
and "I'm so proud of you."
真不敢相信
I just can't believe you could
这么大的事情  你居然瞒着他
keep something like that from him.
你们绝对是我认识最怪的一对情侣了
You guys have got to be the weirdest couple I know.
是吗
Really?
你想不到更怪的了吗
You can't think of anyone weirder?
可以啊
I can,
不过那人就坐在那里呢
but she's sitting right there.
很好
Yes!
我拼Quiver[箭袋]  配合一个3倍加成
I play the word "Quiver" with a triple letter
以及一个2倍加成  得72分
and a double word score for 72 points.
把你的轮椅胎给打爆了吧  霍金
That ought to let the air out of your tires, Hawking.
我的男朋友与史蒂芬·霍金是朋友
Wow, my boyfriend is friends with Stephen Hawking
我的新去屑洗发水味道也不是柏油味
and my new dandruff shampoo doesn't smell like tar.
真是守得云开见月明了啊  艾米
Everything really is coming up, Amy.
的确挺光荣
It is glorious.
当代最具智慧的人之一
One of the greatest intellects of our time
同意与我进行智力上的君子之争
has agreed to engage with me in a gentlemanly battle of wits.
而且我还虐翻了他
And I'm spanking him so hard
估计他带的研究生也要被他虐翻了
his grad students won't be able to sit down.
当一名男性彻底压制另一男性时
You know, when one male dominates another,
他的睾丸酮会上升
his testosterone level rises.
睾丸酮是一种雄性激素
有维持男性第二性征和性欲的作用
说这个干嘛
What's your point?
想到你会有睾丸酮就兴奋嘛
It's exciting to think you might be getting a testosterone level.
我的好友史蒂芬
My friend Stephen
拼了Act[行动]  得18分
just played the word "Act" for 18 points.
是的  我现在直呼他名字
That's right, I call him Stephen now.
我问过他了  他不接受"轮子哥"的绰号
Because I checked, and he was not okay with Wheels.
你可以把他的Act连成Extract[提取]
Oh, you could turn his "Act" into "Extract,"
这样的话分能加倍
and it would be for double points.
艾米
Amy.
你干嘛直接告诉我一个答案呢
Why would you give me a word?
如果我拼了这个字  我就是作弊
Now, if I play "Extract," it would be cheating.
抱歉
Sorry.
不过我可以填一个完全不相关的
Although, I could play the completely unrelated
更好字眼Extract[萃取物  一字多义]
and better word "Extract."
成功避免道德难题
Ethical conundrum avoided.
谢谢你  大脑
Thanks, brain.
意大利面好吃吗
Spaghetti okay?
很"脆"
It's crunchy.
我就爱这样的
Just the way I like it.
好啦  那水我也觉得没烧开
Yeah, I don't think the water was really boiling.
挺好的  我很喜欢啦
It's great. I love it.
听着  我有事情要告诉你
Okay, listen, there's something I need to tell you.
我考虑重返校园有一段时间了
I've been thinking about going back to school for a while now.
所以一个月前
So a couple months ago,
我在一家社区大学报读了历史课
I started taking a history class at the community college.
这真是太棒了  棒极了  超棒的
That's great! Great, great, great!
干嘛拖这么久才告诉我呢
Why wait so long to tell me?
因为我不想你小题大作
I don't want you to make a big deal out of it.
你为什么会这样想我呢
Why do you think I'd be like that?
我懂  你报了一门课  很好啊
I get it, you're taking one class. It's nice.
如果一切顺利
Maybe if it goes well,
可以再报一门  然后变成全日制学生
you take another, you enroll full-time.
对了  记得注意下
Ooh, be sure to keep an eye on
哪些学分是能转修成四年制大学的
which credits transfer to a four-year college.
你现在就是在小题大作
You're making it a big deal.
抱歉  那随便吧
Sorry. Whatever.
都好
It's all good.
总之  就是这样
Anyway, that's it.
我就觉得该知会你一声
I just thought you should know.
我能问问课上得怎么样吗
Am I allowed to ask how the class is going?
相当不错
It's really good.
我们在学有关奴隶的起源
We've been talking about the origins of slavery.
明天就要上交我第一篇论文
Turn in my first paper tomorrow.
好主题  我可以帮你
Great topic. I can help with that.
你可以从很多不同的观点来论述
There are lots of different perspectives you can take:
比如经济  社会  政治
economic, sociological, political...
喂  这是我的论文
Hey, this is my paper.
我的观点就是  奴隶是坏事
And my perspective is that slavery is bad.
我的教授是黑人
Oh, and my professor's black,
所以我确信这就是正确的答案
so I'm pretty sure that's the right answer.
-我能看看吗  -不行
- Can I take a look? - No,
莱纳德  这是我的东西
Leonard, this is my thing.
-好吧  我知道了  -多谢理解
- Okay, I get it. - Thank you.
这像我开始练引体向上时
It's like when I started doing chin-ups;
做不到一个前  我都没脸让你看
I didn't want you to see until I could do one.
顺便说一声  差点就成功了
FYI, really close.
谢谢
Thank you.
现在给我乖乖地吃饭
Now behave yourself and eat your dinner.
晚点  运气好的话
Maybe later, if you're lucky,
你或许可以跟一个大学生上床哟
you get to sleep with a college girl.
真的吗
Really?
我念了四年大学
'Cause I went to four years of college
五年研究生院  这种好事一次都没发生过
and five years of grad school, that never happened once.
下次我跟在印度的客服中心讲话时
I think the next time I have to speak to a call center in India,
我要试着用美国口语
I'm going to try using an American accent.
为什么
Why?
因为用正常声音说话
Because when I use my regular voice,
我会觉得我好像在逗他们玩
I feel like I'm making fun of them.
这理由太可笑了吧
That's ridiculous.
而且你的美国口音烂死了
Not to mention, your American accent is terrible.
伙计  我的口音超棒的
Dude, my accent is brilliant.
我白皮肤的美国朋友们
Hey, my snow-white American friends,
让我们把牛肉放上烤肉架
let's put some cow meat on the barbecue
然后猛吃  直到吃成死胖子
and eat it until we're all obese.
你其实是像这样
This is what you sound like.
我觉得我在用美国口音说话
I think I'm talking in an American accent,
但听起来却是
but it really sounds like
我正戴着一副不合嘴的假牙说话
I'm wearing a set of giant dentures.
谢尔顿  我听起来真的像那样吗
Sheldon, do I really sound like that?
告诉他就是那样
Tell him he sounds like that.
谢尔顿  你没事吧
Sheldon, you okay?
这都三天了
It's been three days.
为什么史蒂芬·霍金还没拼一个字
Why hasn't Stephen Hawking played a word?
那家伙是天才
The guy's a genius.
或许你对他来说  挑战性不够
Maybe you weren't challenging enough for him.
不够挑战性
Not challenging?
我把他虐爆了好吗
I was humiliating the man.
我还在想出一本书  名叫
I was thinking of writing a book called
《时间简史之
A Brief History of the Time
我让史蒂芬·霍金痛哭流涕》
I Made Stephen Hawking Cry Like a Little Girl.
这就是问题所在
There's the problem.
你不能这样打败霍金
You can't beat Hawking like that.
他讨厌输
He hates to lose.
大家都知道他脾气跟小孩一样
Everyone knows the guy's a big baby.
他不应该坐轮椅  他应该坐婴儿车才对
I mean, forget the wheelchair, he should be in a stroller.
真的吗
Really?
有次我跟他共事时
One time when I was working with him,
他说强尼·戴普有参演《黑客帝国》
he said that Johnny Depp was in The Matrix.
我告诉他记错了  可他仍死命坚持
I told him he was wrong, but he kept insisting.
于是我把再网上查出来的结果给他看
So I looked it up online and showed him.
然后第二天  他举办了个披萨派对
Well, the next day, he had a pizza party,
大家都被邀请了  唯独我没有
and everyone got invited but me.
然后他就说
And then he was all,
"可能你的邀请函丢在母体里了吧"
"Your invitation must have gotten lost in the matrix."
上帝啊  我都做了什么啊
Good Lord, what have I done?
烂死了
Terrible.
好吧  高手  那你说印度口音试试
All right, hotshot, let's hear your Indian.
我不能坐上那头大象
I can't sit on that elephant,
因为吃了咖喱  我火烧火燎地想拉肚子
my ass is on fire from eating all this curry.
好吧  说得真好
Okay, yeah, that's pretty good.
拜托是篇好论文
Please be good.
好吧
Okay.
她写作煮饭一样烂
She writes like she cooks.
拼字
Play.
拼字  拼字
Play. Play.
拼字
Play.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
试图用绝地念力
Trying to use a Jedi mind trick
来控制斯蒂芬·霍金
to control Stephen Hawking.
拼字
Play.
他肯定头戴着防念力锡纸帽什么的
He must be wearing a Tin foil hat or something.
我做了件坏事
I did a bad thing.
-会影响到我吗  -不会
- Does it affect me? - No.
那你默默忍受吧
Then suffer in silence.
拼字
Play.
拼字  拼字
Play. Play.
史蒂芬·霍金...
Stephen Hawking...
史蒂芬·霍金...  史蒂芬·霍金
Stephen Hawking... Stephen Hawking.
佩妮报读了一个班
Penny started taking a class.
她写了篇论文  但不给我看
She wrote a paper, she didn't want me to read it,
但我背着她偷偷看完了
I went behind her back and I read it anyway.
史蒂芬·霍金讨厌我
Stephen Hawking hates me.
我不知道怎么办才好
I don't know what to do.
她那论文写的糟透了
I mean, the paper's terrible.
但如果我告诉她  她就知道我看过了
But if I tell her, she'll know that I read it
她一定会很生气
and she'll get really mad.
我把他虐得太惨
I was beating him so bad,
他不想跟我做朋友了
he doesn't want to be friends anymore.
大家都喜欢我  为何史蒂芬·霍金不这样呢
Why does everyone love me except Stephen Hawking?
咱俩讨论的貌似不是同一件事吧
Is it possible we're having two different conversations?
我怎么知道  我又没听你说什么
How would I know? I'm not listening to you.
等一下
Hang on.
有了
Okay.
我们接下来这么干
Here's what we're gonna do.
赛棋钟
Chess clock.
我们每人有5分钟说自己的麻烦
We each get five minutes to talk about our problems.
轮流说
We'll take turns.
每一轮包括自我陈述
Each turn will consist of a statement
以及朋友提出的有益建议
and a helpful response from the friend.
计时开始
Begin.
我在《填字游戏》中虐了史蒂芬·霍金
I humiliated Stephen Hawking in a game of Words with Friends.
结果他不玩了
He stopped playing.
现在我们已不再是朋友了
And now we're not friends anymore.
他可能很忙呢
He's probably busy.
你没必要担心
You're worried about nothing.
再给他几天时间
Give it a couple more days.
他会玩的  你就会发现一切都没事
I'm sure he'll play, and you'll see that everything's fine.
到我了
My turn.
我不能让佩妮交这么一篇烂论文
I can't let Penny hand in a bad paper,
但我如何告诉她这件事
but how do I tell her it's bad
又不让她知道我已经看了呢
without letting her know that I read it?
这难倒我了  现在...
Beats me. Now...
我知道霍金根本没在忙
I know Hawking's not busy
因为我能看到他在跟其他人玩呢
because I can see he's playing other people right now.
也许你太强了
Maybe since you're so good,
他得花时间去思考该怎么下
he's taking his time to meet the challenge.
我希望佩妮能享受在学校...
I want Penny to enjoy school...
沃罗威茨告诉我他是个大孩子
Wolowitz told me he's a big baby!
但我又不知道这事
But I didn't know that,
我连成了"Extract"这个词  得了82分
and I played "Extract" for 82 points.
都是艾米的错  她让我拼这词的
It's all Amy's fault. She told me to play it.
我得跟她割席断交
I have got to cut her loose.
谢尔顿  我还没说完呢
Sheldon, I wasn't done talking.
她明天就要交论文了
She hands in the paper tomorrow.
我知道我帮得了她
I know I could help her.
她是我女朋友...
And she's my girlfriend...
她  她应该准我帮她
I-I should be allowed to help her.
为什么就不准我帮她呢
Why aren't I allowed to help her?
我懂你的烦恼  兄弟
Yeah, I hear you, brother.
不行
No.
你需要给我点建议
You need to give me some advice.
行啊  女人嘛  是吧
Fine. Women, huh?
不行...
No...
要针对我的情况给建议
Specific to my situation.
金发女人嘛  是吧
Blonde women, huh?
设身处地的建议
Empathetic!
-算你倒霉呗  -我不玩了
- It sucks to be you. - I quit.
莱纳德  等下  不要嘛
Leonard, wait. No.
我都听完了你的蠢事
I listened to your dumb thing.
莱纳德  快回来
Leonard, come back.
-干啥  -难怪呢
- What? - Oh, of course,
只有意志薄弱的人才会被操控
it only works on the weak-minded.
早安  阳光小美女
Good morning, sunshine.
莱纳德
Leonard.
才早上8点
It's 8:00 a.M.
相当于三更半夜啊
It's like the middle of the night.
我知道  但我得去上班了
I know, but I have to go to work,
我给你做了早餐
and I made you breakfast.
哇哦  这太贴心了
Oh, wow, that's so sweet.
-这是什么  -在你打开之前
- Hey, what's this? - Uh, before you open that,
我想问你  听过一个童话叫
um, are you familiar with the story of
"精灵和鞋匠"吗
"The Shoemaker and the Elves"?
精灵吗  拜托  莱纳德
Elves? Come on, Leonard.
-现在看《指环王》也太早了吧  -不  不
- It's too early for Lord of the Rings. - No, no.
听我说
Listen, um...
很久很久以前  有一个鞋匠
Once upon a time, there was this shoemaker
他晚上上床睡觉后
and when he went to bed at night,
精灵们会偷偷地
elves would sneak in
趁他入睡时  做漂亮的鞋子给他卖
and they would make all these amazing shoes for him.
当鞋匠第二天一早醒来时
And when the shoemaker woke up in the morning,
他...他会非常开心
he-he would be super happy,
一点也不责怪小精灵们
not mad at the elves at all.
打开吧
Open it.
好吧
Okay.
1619至1865年  南北战争前
"An examination of the economic, cultural,
从经济  文化  政治分析
and political roots of slavery
旧南方地区奴隶制度的根源
in the Old South: 1619 to 1865."
这是什么鬼东西
What the hell is this?
别问我  是一个小精灵做的
Don't ask me. A little elf did it.
让我理理清楚
So let me get this straight.
你没看就猜我的文章会很糟
You just assumed my paper would be bad
所以你写了份新的给我吗
so you wrote one for me?
不  我猜你的文章会很棒  所以我看了
No, I assumed it would be good. Then I read it.
-什么  -不是  我...
- What?! - No, I...
我是说  的确不错
I mean, it was good.
只是还有点地方需要稍加润色
There were just a few things that needed a little polishing.
-什么啊  你把每个词都改了  -那不是事实
- W... You changed every word. - That's not true.
"奴隶制"
"Slavery."
"1619年"
"1619,"
还有上面你的名字  都是你写的呀
your name at the top-- that's all you.
你真是个混蛋
You are such an ass.
这就是为何我报读时
This is exactly why I didn't want to tell you
没第一时间告诉你的原因
I was taking a class in the first place.
请别生气  我只是...
Please don't be upset. I-I just...
我只是不希望你得分太低
I didn't want you ending up with a bad grade
然后灰心丧气  就不再想
and get discouraged and give up on the idea
继续学业了
of going back to school.
是哦  因为我上学
Right, because me being in school
对你来说太重要了
is so important to you.
这样的话  你约会的对象就不仅仅
That way, you wouldn't have to be dating someone
是个服务员
who's only a waitress.
拜托  你知道我不是这个意思
Oh, come on, you know that's not true.
是吗  听好了
Do I? Listen to me.
读书这事得靠我自己
I need to do this on my own.
挂科就挂科  及格就及格
If I fail, I fail. If I pass, I pass.
你明白了吗
Do you get it?
抱歉  我只是想帮忙
I'm sorry. I was just trying to help.
下次别帮了
Yeah, well, next time don't.
还有  既然你这么喜欢讲故事
Oh, and since you like stories so much,
这不是《鞋匠与精灵》  明白吗
this is not "The Shoemaker and the Elves," okay?
这是  "给人一条鱼  他就吃了
This is, "Give a man a fish, he eats it.
教会他捕鱼  他...
Teach a man to fish, he...
会卖鱼什么的"  随便啦  我不知道
sells it or something." Whatever, I don't know!
那也比你强多了  你个大混蛋
It's just a lot better than what you did, you big jerk!
霍金那边有消息吗
You ever hear back from Hawking?
没有
No.
看来我失去他这朋友了
It would appear as if I've lost him.
笨大脑
Stupid brain.
没事的
It'll be okay.
怎么会没事
How can it be okay?
史蒂芬·霍金是天才
Stephen Hawking's a genius
说话又跟机器人一样
and he talks like a robot.
这可是我理想中的完美朋友
It's everything I've ever wanted in a friend.
但如果他这人输不起
Yeah, but if he's a sore loser,
没这个朋友也罢
maybe you're better off without him.
有道理
You're right.
我想我只有尽力把你俩变成柠檬水了
I guess I just have to make lemonade out of the two of you.
他拼字了  他拼字了
He played! He played!
鸡笼弟和雷霆之轮哥又和好了
Coop and Rolling Thunder are together again.
他对这个绰号没意见
He was okay with that nickname.
你现在只要放水让他赢就行了
So, now all you have to do is let him win.
早想到了
Way ahead of you.
我会拼"At"[在]
I will play the word "At"
获得微不足道的两分  输掉比赛
for two measly points, throwing the game
以巩固我和
and thus securing my friendship
世上最聪明的人的友谊
with the smartest man in the world.
你等什么呢  提交答案啊
What are you waiting for? Hit "Send."
下不了手
I can't.
故意放水是智慧上的欺诈
Losing on purpose is intellectually dishonest.
那就别这样
So don't do it.
可我想做霍金的朋友
Oh, but I want to be Hawking's friend.
那就快发啊
So do it.
但如果这样做  我就是个伪君子
No, but if I do, I'll be a phony,
没节操
a sellout,
像好莱坞明星一样假
a Hollywood poser.
那就别这样做
Then don't do it.
我不会
I won't.
这样感觉才对
This feels right.
我妈总是说  对自己要诚实
My mother always said, "to thine own self be true."
好样的
Good for you.
她也告诉我全世界的动物
'Course she also told me that every animal in the world
上了一条船  她懂什么呀  发送
got on one boat, so what does she know? And send.
几天没见到你了
Haven't heard from you in a couple days.
你还在生我的气吗
You still mad at me?
没
Nope.
我没有理由
I have no reason to...
生你的气[谐音be mad at you]
"B" mad at you.
没错  我的论文
That's right. On my paper.
不是你的  是我的得了B-  你这个混蛋精灵
Not yours, mine, you punk-ass elf.
我不知道说什么好
I don't know what to say.
这样说
Hmm, how about,
"老天  佩妮  你比我想象中要聪明
"Gee, Penny, you're smarter than I thought.
虽说上学的是你
You may be the one in school,
但学到一课的是我
but I'm the one who learned a lesson.
我好蠢  佩妮  真滴"
I'm so stupid, Penny. Duh..."
她学你学得惟妙惟肖啊
She sounds exactly like you!
莱纳德有啥反应
How'd it go with Leonard?
我想他不会再犯这种错误了
I don't think he'll be making that mistake again.
太好了
Good.
我知道我这是多此一举
So, I know this goes without saying,
但如果你们告诉莱纳德
but if either of you tell Leonard
你们帮我重写了论文
you helped me rewrite this paper,
我会用一袋橙子打爆你们俩
I will beat you both with a bag of oranges.
-知道  -明白
- Got it. - Understood.
姐妹们  这次论文得了B-
Now, ladies, we got a B-minus on this paper.
我认为如果我们一起努力
I think if we put our heads together,
下次就会得个A
on the next one we could get an "A."
可我们是故意让你得B-的  这样才可信
Uh, but we got you a B-minus on purpose to make it believable.
可信
Believable?
你是说我不聪明吗
You saying I'm not smart?
-不是  -你很聪明
- No, no! - You're smart.
这还差不多
That's better.
感觉我又回到了高中
I feel like I'm in high school again.
对  帮舞会皇后做功课  这样她才喜欢我们
Yeah, doing the prom queen's homework so she'll like us.
是啊
I know.
这招终于管用了
It's finally working.
是史蒂芬·霍金
It's Stephen Hawking.
快接  我想听
Answer it. I want to hear.
霍金教授
Professor Hawking,
很高兴你打电话过来
how nice of you to call.
你好
Hello.
我玩游戏玩得很开心  库珀博士
I really enjoyed our game, Dr. Cooper.
我也是
Oh, me, too.
还是该叫你窝囊废博士呢
Or should I say Dr. Loser?
哈哈哈
Ha, ha, ha.
是的  恭喜你
Yes, congratulations.
你是实至名归的赢家
You won fair and square.
非常厉害  先生
Uh, very impressive, sir.
你喜欢"脑筋急转弯"吗
Do you like brain teasers?
我爱玩"脑筋急转弯"
Oh, I love brain teasers.
谢尔顿·库珀
What does Sheldon Cooper
与黑洞有什么共同点
and a black hole have in common?
都很烂[吸力]
They both suck.
气死你  气死你
Neener neener.